prestoclassical.co.uk 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy and Cookies | Presto Music

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information which you give Presto Music when you use this website. Presto Music is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected: we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page; you should check this page periodically to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 24th May 2018.

## What we collect

We may collect and store the following information:

  * your name
  * your postal address, billing address and email address
  * your telephone number
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

Some of these details may be passed onto our distribution partners in order to fulfil your order. Some of them, along with your payment details, will be passed on to our payment providers in order to complete your transaction.

## What we do with the information which we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record-keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send newsletter emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We will only contact you by email. We may use your responses to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie allows that website to respond to you as an individual and to tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Cookies are also used to help analyse web traffic and to let the website know when you visit particular pages.

On our website we use cookies to remember your basket details and address information which you have asked us to save, along with linking you to your account if you have one: you will be unable to buy products from us online without them. We also use them to enhance your experience and for statistical analysis. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept them, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us in writing as soon as possible and any necessary amendments will be made promptly.

Revision date: 17th July 2018
